A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Company truck for the Grabole Company: Roofing and Spray Painting Contractors, New Market, Va. Side view.Approx.1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0054; 4x5
- Grabole Company truck, parked at a job site.Approx.1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0055; 4x5
- Same job site for the Grabole Company as seen in 0052.Approx. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0056; 4x5
- Same job site for the Grabole Company as seen in 0052.Approx. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0057; 4x5
- Closer-up view of the tower at the job site for the Grabole Company, as seen in 0052.Approx. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0058; 4x5
- Same job site for the Grabole Company as seen in 0052.Approx. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0059; 4x5
- Company truck for Feeder’s Feed, Inc., Timberville, Va. Side view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0060; 4x5
- Company truck for Feeder’s Feed, Inc., Timberville, Va. Side view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0061; 4x5
- Inside of the company truck for Feeder’s Feed, Inc., Timberville, Va. Side view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0062; 4x5
- A row of company trucks for Triplett and Vehrencamp, a farming and hardware store, Mt. Jackson, Va. The drivers are standing next to their trucks.1950, Image: P0002.02.0063; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0063.1950, Image: P0002.02.0063a; 4x5
- A row of company trucks for Triplett and Vehrencamp, a farming and hardware store, Mt. Jackson, Va. View without the drivers.1950, Image: P0002.02.0064; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0064.1950, Image: P0002.02.0064a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0064.1950, Image: P0002.02.0064b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0064.1950, Image: P0002.02.0064c; 4x5
- Armour company truck, front diagonal view.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.02.0065; 2.5x3.5
- Company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va. View of the side, from the ground. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0066; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0067.
- View of a roadway with two cars.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0067; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0066.
- Back view of a company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0068; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0069.
- Side view of a company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0069; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0068.
- Back view of a company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0070; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0071.
- Back view of a company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0071; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0070.
- Back view of a company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va. View of people marking the road nearby with tape.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0072; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0073.
- Side view of a company truck for “Smith’s,” Staunton, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0073; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0072.
- Long line of some sort of company or industry trucks parked on the side of a street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0074; 2.5x3.5
  Heavy amounts of blue dye due to film deterioration.
- A company truck for Seller’s Motor Company, parked next to two other vehicles.Approx. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.02.0075; 2.5x3.5
- A number of private automobiles parked in a field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0076; 2.5x2.5
  Series 3b, Motor Vehicles: Private,” begins. Housed with 0077.
- A number of private automobiles parked in a field. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0077; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0076.
- Two private vehicles parked inside of a garage or shop.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0078; 2.5x3.5
- A private automobile parked next to a Coca-Cola advertisement and sign that says “Happy Motoring.”c. 1935-1945, Image: P0002.02.0079; 1.5x2
  Housed with 0080.
- Same private automobile as in 0075, view from the front.c. 1935-19456, Image: P0002.02.0080; 1.5x2
  Housed with 0079.
- A private automobile parked alone in a field with a road/power lines in the background. View from the front of the vehicle; Virginia license plate 614-853.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0081; 4x5
- Side view of a private automobile, Virginia license plate 614-853.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0082; 4x5
- Side view of a private automobile, presumably the same as in 0077 and 0078.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0083; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0083.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0083a; 4x5
- Diagonal view of a private automobile, Virginia license plate 614-853.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0084; 4x5
- Alternate diagonal view of a private automobile, Virginia license plate 614-853.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0085; 4x5
- Private automobile, parked on a street or roundabout. Side view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0086; 2.5x3.5
- Private automobile, parked in front of a building with a number of other cars.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0087; 2.5x3.5
- Private automobile, parked in a parking lot or side street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0088; 2.5x3.5
- Private automobile, parked in a field.c. 1950-1955, Image: P0002.02.0089; 4x5
- View of the engine underneath a hood of a car.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0090; 4x5
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0091; 4x5
  Series 4a, “Civil and Armed Services: Police,” begins.
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill, smiling or laughing.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0092; 4x5
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill, alternate pose.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0093; 4x5
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0094; 4x5
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0095; 4x5
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0096; 4x5
- Portrait of a Mount Jackson police officer.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097a; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097b; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097c; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097d; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097e; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097f; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097g; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0097h; 2.5x3.5
- Portrait of a Mount Jackson police officer, smiling.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0098; 2.5x3.5
- A number of Mount Jackson police officers and other men standing outside and looking at something on the ground that is not pictured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0099; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a Virginia State Police car.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0100; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0101, 0102, and 0103.
- A small white house; possibly taken to test the film or camera.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0101; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0100, 0102, and 0103.
- A photography magazine and a few other items: possibly taken to test the film or camera.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0102; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0100, 0101, and 0103.
- View of a large building in an urban area; function unknown.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0103; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0100, 0101, and 0102.
- Front view of the Mount Jackson Fire Department, with three trucks pictured.1949, Image: P0002.02.0104; 4x5
  Series 4b, “Civil and Armed Services: Fire,” begins.
- Front view of the Mount Jackson Fire Department, with three trucks pictured.1949, Image: P0002.02.0105; 4x5
- Diagonal view of the Mount Jackson Fire Department.1949, Image: P0002.02.0106; 4x5
- Diagonal view of the Mount Jackson Fire Department.1949, Image: P0002.02.0107; 4x5
- New Market Fire Department Open House; view of four men posing next to a nineteenth-century “fire truck.”c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0108; 4x5
- A group of firemen/officers posing next to a nineteenth century “fire truck.”c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0109; 4x5
- A group of firemen/officers posing in front of a fire truck with flower bouquets on either side and a large sign that says “New Market Fire Dept. New Market Va.”c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0110; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0110.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0110a; 4x5
- New Market Fire Department Open House; a group of women posing in a kitchen with numerous flowers.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0111; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0111.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0111a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0111.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0111b; 4x5
- New Market Fire Department Open House: inside view of the kitchen.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0112; 4x5
- New Market Fire Department Open House: view of group of women leaning against the counter in the kitchen.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0113; 4x5
- New Market Fire Department Open House: large group of men, women, and children dining together in a large room with a buffet table at the head.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0114; 4x5
- Front view of the Broadway Volunteer Fire Department.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0115; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0115.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0115a; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; three men in suits standing behind a podium.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0116; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0446.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0116a; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; a man in a suit standing at a podium, with other men sitting in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0117; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; a man in a suit standing at a podium, with other men sitting in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0118; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; a man in a suit on a platform, extending a help hand or passing an object to a woman walking towards him.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0119; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; two men in suits shaking hands behind a podium.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0120; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; two men in suits about to shake hands behind a podium.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0121; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; five men and one woman posing behind a podium.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0122; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; group of nine women in the kitchen pouring beverages.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0123; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; group of four men in suits looking over a program or booklet.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0124; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house; view of a man playing a piano with a woman and four other man sitting/standing nearby.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0125; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Volunteer Fire Department, front view with two trucks pictured. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0126; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0126.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0126a; 4x5
- Timberville Volunteer Fire Department, diagonal view with two trucks pictured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0127; 4x5
- Timberville Volunteer Fire Department, diagonal view with two trucks pictured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0128; 4x5
- Vehicle belonging to the Department of Interior, Bureau of Mines.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0129; 4x5
  Series 4c, “Civil and Armed Services: Government and Military,” begins.
- Vehicle belonging to the Department of Interior, Bureau of Mines, back view. Two men stand beside it.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0130; 4x5
- Vehicle belonging to the Department of Interior, Bureau of Mines, with two men working nearby.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0131; 4x5
- A group of armed men holding a meeting or rally, presumably a local militia or other types of soldier.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0132; 2.5x3.5
- A group of armed men holding a meeting or rally, presumably a local militia or other types of soldier.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0133; 2.5x3.5
- An assembly of armed men, presumably a local militia or other types of soldier.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0134; 2.5x3.5
- A man in a soldier uniform standing against the outer wall of a building. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0135; 1.25x1.75
- Two men in military uniforms posing against the outer wall of a building.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0136; 1.25x1.75
- Three men in military uniform standing/sitting on the side of the road near a stop sign; they appear to be hitchhiking. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0137; 1.25x1.75
- Two men in military uniform posing on the side of the road with an automobile in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0138; 1.25x1.75
- Three men in military uniform posing against the outer wall of a building; one is making an obscene gesture with his hands.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0139; 1.25x1.75
- Two men in military uniform, one sitting at a desk and the other looking over his shoulder.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0140; 2.5x3.5
- Two men in military uniform, sitting inside the barracks, one administering some sort of driving test to the other.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0141; 2.5x3.5
- An assembly of soldiers in a space that seems to double as sleeping quarters and as an office.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0142; 2.5x3.5
- Two soldiers painting or finishing the floor of the sleeping quarters.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0143; 2.5x3.5
- A man in a military uniform sitting at a desk.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0144; 2.5x3.5
- Three men in military uniform standing/sitting in an office.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0145; 2.5x3.5
- A group of members of the CCC gathered in a rough circle in a wooded area.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0146; 2.5x3.5
- A large group of CCC workers piled onto a number of vehicles in a hilly, wooded area.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0147; 2.5x3.5
- A large group of CCC workers and vehicles; taken from a distance.Approx 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0148; 2.5x3.5
- A group of CCC workers sitting in an overgrown field.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0149; 2.5x3.5
- A group of CCC workers sitting in an overgrown field facing a dirt road that is lined with various automobiles.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0150; 2.5x3.5
- A group of CCC workers gathered around a trash canister.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0151; 2.5x3.5
- A larger group of CCC workers standing in a heavily wooded area.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0152; 2.5x3.5
- Various CCC workers gathered together, sitting on the ground, and sitting in the back of a truck.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0153; 2.5x3.5
- A group of CCC workers posing for the camera.Approx. 1933-1942, Image: P0002.02.0154; 2.5x3.5
- A large group of Spanish War Veterans and their wives posing with a sign welcoming them to the Orkney Springs Hotel for a reunion.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0155; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0155.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0155a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0155.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0155b; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, view of a veteran in uniform.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0156; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0157.
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, view of a veteran.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0157; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0156.
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, view of two veterans in uniform.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0158; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0159.
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, view of two veterans in uniform.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0159; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0158.
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, view of two veterans in uniform shaking hands.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0160; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0161.
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, view of two veterans in uniform.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0161; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0160.
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, a number of people seated underneath a pavilion.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0162; 2.5x3.5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, a man pulling on a rope above him.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0163; 2.5x3.5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, a large group of people gathered in a reception hall of sorts, with two very well dressed women addressing eachother in the foreground.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0164; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion at the Orkney Springs Hotel, a large gathering of men and women in very formal dress.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0165; 4x5
- A number of wives or other female family members of Spanish War Veterans gathered in a parlor of the Orkney Springs Hotel for a reunion.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0166; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a large group of finely dressed men and women pose for the camera.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0167; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; two elaborately dressed elderly women.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0168; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; group of women gathered in a parlor.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0169; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; elderly woman posing with numerous other men and women in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0170; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; an elderly man and two women socializing in a large room, with numerous other men and women in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0171; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; an elderly man and woman socializing in a large room.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0172; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a large procession of elaborately dressed men and women into a very large hall or room.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0173; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a number of elderly men socializing.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0174; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; view of an elaborately dressed couple with others socializing in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0175; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; view of an elaborately dressed couple with others socializing in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0176; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; group of finely dressed women.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0177; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; group of elderly men and women socializing in a large room.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0178; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; man in a suit posing with a large group of other men and women in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0179; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a large group of men and women in a large hall, possibly dancing. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0180; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; four finely dressed women posed in front of a background of numerous socializing men and women.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0181; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; five men in suits posing for the camera.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0182; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a large group of finely dressed men and women in a large hall or room. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0183; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a group of five men standing outside.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0184; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a large group of men and women posing outside. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0185; 4x5
- Spanish War Veterans Reunion, Orkney Springs Hotel; a large group of men and women posing outside with the United States flag and another flag posted on either side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0186; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0186.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0186a; 4x5
- A group of young men and women standing in front of Timberville (High) School.1949, Image: P0002.02.0187; 4x5
  Series 5a, “School Photos: Timberville High School,” begins. Note: Until 1952, this school served as a combination grade and high school.
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0187.1949, Image: P0002.02.0187a; 4x5
- A group of young men and women standing in front of Timberville (High) School. 1949, Image: P0002.02.0188; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0188.1949, Image: P0002.02.0188a; 4x5
- Group photo of the members of the Timberville (High) School band.1949, Image: P0002.02.0189; 4x5
- Group photo of the members of the Timberville (High) School band with their instruments held up.1949, Image: P0002.02.0190; 4x5
- Three young men in the wood shop class at Timberville (High) School.1949, Image: P0002.02.0191; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, women’s basketball team, posing with their coach.1949, Image: P0002.02.0192; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, women’s basketball team, lined up in front of the school with their coach.1949, Image: P0002.02.0193; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0193.1949, Image: P0002.02.0193a; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, women’s basketball team, view from the air of them lined up on the basketball court.1949, Image: P0002.02.0194; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, a women’s sports team in uniform posing with their coach in front of the school; possibly tennis.1949, Image: P0002.02.0195; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0525.1949, Image: P0002.02.0195a; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, women’s softball team posing with their coach in front of the school.1949, Image: P0002.02.0196; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0196.1949, Image: P0002.02.0196a; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, men’s baseball team posing in front of the school.1949, Image: P0002.02.0197; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0197.1949, Image: P0002.02.0197a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0197.1949, Image: P0002.02.0197b; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, a men’s sports team, possibly track and field.1949, Image: P0002.02.0198; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0198.1949, Image: P0002.02.0198a; 4x5
- Timberville (High) School, men’s baseball team posing with their coach in the basketball gym.1949, Image: P0002.02.0199; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0199.1949, Image: P0002.02.0199a; 4x5
- Timberville School, a group of very young boys and girls with their teacher.1949, Image: P0002.02.0200; 4x5
- Timberville School, a group of very young boys and girls with their teacher.1949, Image: P0002.02.0201; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, young men and women in a classroom working as the teacher walks up one of the aisles.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0202; 2.5x3.5
  Series 5b, “School Photos: Broadway High School,” begins. Note: Until 1952, this school served as a combination grade and high school.
- Broadway (High) School, young men and women studying in a library.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0203; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, young boys and girls in a classroom facing the blackboard, where the teacher is using a pointer.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0204; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, a group of young girls and boys sitting in a semi-circle in a classroom watching another young girl give a presentation at the blackboard.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0205; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, a group of young boys and girls sitting at a table inside of a classroom.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0206; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, four young boys and girls giving a presentation to a classroom full of their peers.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0207; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, a group of young boys and girls looking at books in the library.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0208; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, large group of young men and women eating in the cafeteria.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0209; 2.5x3.5